她也一样  不过表现在性爱上
Okay, this is her, but sexually.
她和李欧·博曼上床
She slept with Leo Brockman,
除丈夫外  不曾与人发生关系的她
Never having been to bed with anyone before but her husband,
仿佛打开了潘多拉的魔盒
And suddenly, the genie was outta the bottle!
她喜欢和博曼上床
She liked sleeping with Brockman,
喜欢和博曼的朋友们上床
And she liked sleeping with Brockman's friends,
博曼的熟人  博曼熟人的熟人
Brockman's acquaintances, Brockman's acquaintances' acquaintances.
博曼把她的摄影集带给摩根斯
Brockman took her photos to Morgenstern. he loved them.
摩根斯很喜欢  决定展出
He decided to show them in his gallery.
展出后  人们都觉得才华横溢  淳朴自然
When he did, everyone thought they were great. a brilliant primitive.
摩根斯就成了她的裙下之臣
Soon Morgenstern would become smitten with her.
她先和博曼同居  后与摩根斯同居
First she moved in with Brockman. then she moved in with Morgenstern.